http://www.thenappylady.co.uk/privacy-policy.html

Nappy Advice & Customer ServiceNappy Advice Questionnaire© Find The Most Suitable Nappies For Your BabyCloth Versus DisposablesChoosing your cloth nappy systemParts Of A Nappy SystemUsing & Washing Your Nappy SystemNappy ProblemsNappy Fitting GuideEC- Elimination CommunicationReusable Sanitary Wear AdviceDelivery & Returns InformationNappy Brands WarrantiesCouncil VouchersContact UsPress CoverageTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyMailing ListOur StoryTeam Nappy LadyRight To Cancel FormHerts Reusable Nappy Scheme - How To RedeemPrivacy PolicyIt's very simple: I run The Nappy Lady in a way in which I as a mother expect another company to treat me. And I am fussy.Who are we?We are The Nappy Lady Ltd the largest independent specialist cloth nappy retailer in the UK. The Nappy Lady is a Limited company owned by Wendy Richards. Our registered company number is 7927974. Our registered address is 2 North Ave, Farnham, GU9 0RDHow do we collect information from you?We obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you contact us about products and services, place an order, or if you register to receive one of our ad hoc newsletters. What type of information is collected from you? The personal information we collect might include your name, address, email address, IP address, and information regarding when you accessed our website and the last page you looked at. If you complete our advice questionnaire we will hold details of your nappy preferences and priorities which we will use to send you a personal recommendation. Once your recommendation is sent to you the data remains on file for 12 months in case you have a query at a later date (ie after baby is born). We do not access or use this data again unless you contact us and ask for help regarding your original questionnaire. If you purchase a product from us, your card information is not held by us, it is collected by our third party payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions, as explained below.How is your information used?We may use your information to: process orders that you have submitted dealing with any queries you have about your order seek your views or comments on the services we provide notify you of changes to our services send you emails about new products or services that may interest youWe review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfil our statutory obligations (for example the VAT paid on your order). We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with us.Who has access to your information?We will NEVER sell or rent your information to third parties. We will NEVER share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.Third Party Service Providers working on our behalf:We may pass your information to our third party courier/delivery services providers such as Royal Mail and DPD for the purpose of delivering your parcel. We only disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver the parcel and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own direct marketing purposes.Please be reassured that we will not release your information to third parties for them to use for their own direct marketing purposes, unless you have requested us to do so, or we are required to do so by law, for example, by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime.When you are using our secure online payment pages, your payment is processed by a third party payment processor, who specialises in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions. If you have any questions regarding secure transactions, please contact us.We may transfer your personal information to a third party as part of a sale of some or all of our business and assets to any third party or as part of any business restructuring or reorganisation, or if we’re under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply our terms of use or to protect the rights, property or safety of our  customers. However, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.Your choicesYou have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. If you do not want to receive direct marketing communications from us about our exciting products and services, then when you create an account leave the box unticked for mailing options. We will not contact you for marketing purposes unless you have given your prior consent. You can change your marketing preferences at any time by contacting us by email: info@thenappylady.co.uk or telephone on 01252 372 266.How you can access and update your informationThe accuracy of your information is important to us. You can update your details by logging into your account on the website. You can also contact us and we can do it for you. We can be contacted at: info@thenappylady.co.uk or write to us at The Nappy Lady Ltd, Unit C, Linsford Business Park, Linsford Lane, Mytchett, GU16 6DL . Alternatively, you can telephone 01252 372 266.You have the right to ask for a copy of the information The Nappy Lady Ltd holds about you (we may charge £10 for information requests) to cover our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your informationWhen you give us personal information, we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely. Any sensitive information (such as credit or debit card details) is encrypted and protected with the following software 128 Bit encryption on SSL. When you are on a secure page, a lock icon will appear in the URL bar.Non-sensitive details (your email address etc.) are transmitted normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Where we have given (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our websites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.Use of cookiesLike many other websites, the The Nappy Lady Ltd uses cookies. 'Cookies' are small pieces of information sent by an organisation to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow that website to recognise you when you visit. They collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual. For example, we use cookies to store your country preference. This helps us to improve our website and deliver a better more personalised service. It is possible to switch off cookies by setting your browser preferences. For more information on how to switch off cookies on your computer, visit our full cookies policy. Turning cookies of may result in a loss of functionality when using our website.Links to other websites Our website may contain links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our website‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our website. In addition, if you linked to our website from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site.Review of this PolicyWe keep this Policy under regular review. This Policy was last updated in October 2020.Get in Touch! Contact Us Our Advice Questionnaire Customer Testimonials Customer Service Delivery & Returns Help & FAQs Help Guides & Advice Video Demonstrations About The Nappy Lady Our Privacy PolicyOur Nappy Range Shape Sized Nappies Birth to Potty Nappies Pocket Nappies All in One Nappies All in Twos Nappies Flat, Pad & Prefold Nappies Nappy Wraps Nappy Boosters Nappy Liners Nappy Trial & Full Kits Nappy Hire Kits Reusable Swim Nappies Trainer Pants & Potty TrainingNappy Accessories Nappy Buckets & Bags Nappy Washing Detergent Essential Accessories Washable Wipes Nappy Creams & Baby Skin Care Bed Protectors & Change MatsJust for Mums Washable Breast Pads Reusable Sanitary Wear StoreYour Requirements Quick Drying Nappies Night Time Nappies Newborn Nappies UK Nappies Nappies for Tall Children Natural Material Nappies Nappies for Hot Climates Baby Essentials Baby Accessories Baby CarriersSpecial Offers Clearance Items Multibuy Offers Help & Advice Help Videos Guide to Cloth Nappies Cloth vs Disposable Nappies Parts of a Nappy System Choosing Your Nappy System Nappy Concerns & Problems Guide to Eco-Disposables Elimination CommunicationWe accept most major credit and debit cards as well as payments via PayPal. Secure shopping provided by SagePay.
Call us: 01252 372266
Lines open from 9.30am until 2.00pm, Monday to Friday. At all other times, please email us. Copyright © 1999 - 2020 The Nappy Lady Ltd. All rights reserved. Award winning nappy help and expertise since 1999.Contact Us| Terms & Conditions| Privacy Policy| Site MapSaving The World One Nappy At A Time©New Account / Sign In / Wish List£0.00 (0)ViewShop MenuReusable NappiesShaped Sized NappiesBirth to Potty NappiesPocket NappiesAll in One NappiesAll in Twos NappiesFlat, Pad & Prefold NappiesNappies for ECNewborn NappiesEco-DisposablesMore NappiesNappy WrapsNappy BoostersNappy LinersTrial NappiesFull Nappy KitsNappy Hire KitsReusable Swim NappiesTrainer Pants & Potty TrainingChild Onwards IncontinenceNappy AccessoriesNappy Buckets & BagsNappy Washing DetergentEssential AccessoriesWashable WipesNappy Creams & Skin CareBed Protectors & Change MatsMuslinsBaby EssentialsBaby AccessoriesJust for MumsWashable BreastpadsThe Reusable Sanitary Wear StoreShop by RequirementShop by BrandQuick Drying NappiesNight Time NappiesNewborn NappiesMade in the UKNappies for Tall ChildrenWool Nappy WrapsNatural NappiesNappies for Hot ClimatesNappy AdviceHelp VideosAccessories, Boosters, SwimmingGetting StartedIndividual NappiesMiscellaneousNappy WrapsTerry Squares & Prefold NappiesTrainer PantsNappy AdviceADVICE QUESTIONNAIRECloth vs Disposable NappiesChoosing Your Nappy SystemWhich Reusable Nappy Brand?Parts of a Nappy SystemUsing & Washing Cloth NappiesWool Nappy & AdviceNappy Concerns & ProblemsNappy Fitting GuideElimination CommunicationQuick Links Top ArticlesWhat You Need - Shopping ListParts of a Nappy SystemTypes of Nappy SystemsWhich Nappy Liners? Leak Proof Night NappiesHow to Wash & Dry Cloth NappiesHow To Strip WashCloth Nappies & Hip MovementContactHelp & FAQsContact UsDelivery & ReturnsOur StoryTeam Nappy LadyPress CoverageNappy Brands WarrantiesReal Nappies for LondonFrequently Asked QuestionsWhat our customers say...Council VouchersPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsAdd to Mailing List
